

Cory Swanson

Programming & Design

303.709.4337 | cory.swanson1@gmail.com www.coryswanson.net | linkedin.com/in/cory-swanson

AFFILIATION

COLORADO EVANS SCHOLARS

I was awarded a Chick Evans Caddie Scholarship to attend CU for four years on a full room-board-tuition scholarship. The requirements to become an Evans Scholar involve having an outstanding caddie record, excellent academics, demonstrated financial need, and outstanding character.

SKILLS

ADOBE

I have exceptional skills in the Adobe suite. Not only in **Illustrator** and **Photoshop**, but also programs like **Acrobat**, Indesign, Dreamweaver, and Lightroom.

WEB DEVELOPMENT

I have a good handle on the basics of **HTML**, **CSS**, and Command-line **Git**. I am passionate about learning harder concepts like JavaScript and related frameworks, PHP and SQL.

I'm a quick learner and diligent worker whether alone or in a group.

EXPERIENCE

BOULDER COUNTRY CLUB

GOLF CADDIE • MAY 2011 - JULY 2014

Ensured a bright and rewarding round of golf for members. Paced yardages, read greens, advised club selection, and carried members' bags while maintaining a lively mood.

MEMBER SERVICES • APRIL 2015 - MAY 2016

Greeted every member as they arrived. Was responsible for replacing range balls, tidying the immediate grounds, and being knowledgeable about events happening at the club.

BENT SPOKE DESIGNS

SOLE PROPRIETOR • NOVEMBER 2016 - MAY 2018

Forming logos for local startups, student groups at the University of Colorado, and the Colorado Evans Scholars.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO, BOULDER

BS - FINANCE • MAY 2018

Overall GPA: 3.0 Business GPA: 3.0

Neglecting to choose an emphasis within finance, I opted for a mix of investment management and personal finance.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

COMMUNITY CYCLES

BICYCLE MECHANIC • MAY 2012 - JULY 2015

Assisted customers with repairs, purchases, questions regarding how to fix bicycle components. Completely disassembled bikes to be used for parts and recycled what couldn't be used. Hand built showroom bikes to be sold from spare parts.

JIBERISH MENSWEAR

WAREHOUSING • NOVEMBER 2016 - JANUARY 2017

Packed and shipped Black Friday and Cyber Monday orders. Reorganized the entire warehouse in an ergonomic way. Double checked orders to ensure minimal wrong-item returns. Packed and moved all warehouse contents to a larger storage facility.